



## **TERRY HAIRE**

Software Engineer



24-07-1996



Forelstraat 2, Almere Nederland



+316 1722 8523



terry.wilson.h@gmail.com



terry-haire

## **SKILLS**

Python • Java 80% PHP 80% 90% CSS 70% 90% 70%

## **SOCIAL**





### **ABOUT ME**

My passion is to write code and to create innovative solutions. I am currently a co owner of two companies, but they only require infrequent maintenance from me. Therefore I'm available for new experiences.

My experience running my own company has given me the knowledge and experience to quickly find effective and feasible solutions, which has made me a capable software engineer. Working with my partners and other businesses has also given me the communication skills to become a good person to work with, who is always excited about moving the team forward and is also capable of leadership.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**



# 2019 - Present Software Developer | Boiling Bot

As the software developer of Boiling Bot, I am able to provide the tools and guidance for our users to get limited sneakers, giving them the edge against millions of people around the world.





# 2019 - Present Technical Director | Sneaker Bricks

As founder of sneaker.bricks, I kickstarted our sales platforms, and gained experience working with customers.







## **EDUCATION**



2018 - 2022

# BSc Computer Science | Universiteit van **Amsterdam**

Key modules include:

- Project Software Engineering
- Project Webdevelopment and Databases
- Datastructures
- Modern Databases
- Algorithms and Complexity
- Programming Languages
- Linear Algebra
- Discrete Maths and Logic
- Networks and Network Security

# **Work Experience Details**

#### Software Developer | Boiling Bot

Boiling Bot is an autocheckout service that automatically purchases limited items. These items are out of stock within seconds and require a lot of luck and patience. Automation of the purchasing process assures users they will get the item they want and also allows them to purchase the same item multiple times for reselling purposes, thus generating passive income.

Boiling Bot automatically scales by creating and destroying virtual machines as needed, depending on the amount of users.

#### **Related Skills**

- Bot Protection
- Tracking
- Monitoring
- Scraping
- Website Testing
- White Hat Hacking
- Cybersecurity

#### **Technology Stack**

Web UI Frontend Stack:

- CSS3
- HTML5
- Vue.js

Web UI Backend Stack:

- MongoDB
- Node.js
- Express

#### Bot:

- Python
- PostgreSQL
- Azure Active Directory
- Azure Blob Storage
- Azure Virtual Machines
- Azure Powershell

#### **Technical Director | Sneaker Bricks**

Sneaker Bricks is our sales platform where we sell limited sneakers, mostly retrieved through Boiling Bot. It started on marktplaats, where I sold virtual reality headsets at the start of the COVID19 pandemic. After switching to sneakers, it has continued to grow into a stable business.

I also do the accounting for Sneaker Bricks. I use the bunq API to automatically process transactions. In case a transaction cannot be automatically processed, the person responsible for the transaction will be notified. Then they can use a simple online form to describe the transaction.

#### Skills

- Marketing
- Customer Service
- · Business Relations
- Accounting
- Management
- Teamwork

#### **Technology Stack**

Website:

- Shopify
- · Liquid (Shopify)

Accounting:

- Bung API
- Flask Python

# **Other Projects**

#### Fallout 4 - Mod 1 (2016)

This mod has over 224.000 views on nexusmods. It was also featured on multiple videos and got over 600.000 views on one of them. I used linear algebra to adjust the position of nodes in certain game objects which were not made for this context in the game.

#### Link

#### Videos

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c0wDsBKr95s

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Bh16RO98UE

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yxgnCNOUGU8

#### **Technology Stack**

- Delphi (Pascal) scripting for FO4Edit a mod tool
- Nifskope a mod tool
- Creation Kit official mod tool

#### Fallout 4 - Mod 2 (2016)

Another mod with over 130.000 views on nexusmods. Using Pascal scripting, I deleted unwanted objects from the gameworld.

• Delphi (Pascal) scripting for FO4Edit - a mod tool

#### Link

https://www.nexusmods.com/fallout4/mods/3022

#### Fallout New Vegas to Fallout 4 (2019)

A project to 'remaster' the game Fallout: New Vegas by putting it in the Creation Engine used by Fallout 4. Got as far as converting the entire worldspace, but none of the gameplay. It is currently on hiatus. I wrote over 5000 lines in Delphi and even more in C++ for this project.

#### **Technology Stack**

- Delphi (Pascal)
- C++